export type QuestionPoolType = {
    question: string,
    answers: string[],
    correct_answer: number
}
export const QuestionPool: QuestionPoolType[] = [
    {
        question: "What game Genre best describes Ascension?",
        answers: ["Battle Royale", "MOBA", "PVP Race", "All of the above"],
        correct_answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What do players win in normal mode?",
        answers: ["Paragons", "Runes", "PS tokens", "All of the above"],
        correct_answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What additional features are planned for future development?",
        answers: ["Tournaments", "Leaderboards", "High risk / high reward games", "All of the above"],
        correct_answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "When does The Parallel hope to have the game ready for Main-Net?",
        answers: ["June", "May", "April", "None of the above"],
        correct_answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Whoâ€™s the main boss in Ascension?",
        answers: ["NoGo", "HuGo", "Paratrooper", "None of the above"],
        correct_answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What do you need to play Ascension?",
        answers: ["A paragon with 200 Power level", "Runic Energy", "All of the above"],
        correct_answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How can you refill runic energy?",
        answers: ["Winning", "PRL tokens", "PS tokens and/or wait"],
        correct_answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Parallel designed to become?",
        answers: ["a game", "a platform", "a metaverse", "all of the above"],
        correct_answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is a Paragon?",
        answers: ["A Playable Character", "A World Structure", "NPCs", "A Parallel NFT made from Runes"],
        correct_answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What do you need to craft a Paragon?",
        answers: ["Para-Art, Runes", "Para-Art, PS", "Runes, PRL, PS & Para-Art", "PS, Runes, PRL"],
        correct_answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How does the power of NFT Paragons effect in Ascension game?",
        answers: ["Running speed of in-game character", "Number of playtime", "In-game character's appearance", "All of the above"],
        correct_answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What are the main supply sources of Runes until now?",
        answers: ["NFT Boxes", "Mining Program", "Marketplace", "A, B"],
        correct_answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What can landowners do in The Parallel?",
        answers: ["Host an Event", "Build a mini game", "Sell & rent", "All of the above"],
        correct_answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which kind of game can be integrated into The Parallel?",
        answers: ["MOBA", "RPG", "Casual game", "All of the above"],
        correct_answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How many ranks of rune are there?",
        answers: ["8", "10", "12", "15"],
        correct_answer: 2
    },
]
